(Sheldon:)and I don't want
to disappoint them.
(Amy:)And the mood continues
to change.
(Sheldon:)No, and also, I don't
want to disappoint you. I...
(Sheldon:)You know, come on.
It's your birthday.
(Sheldon:)I can soldier through this.
H-Hold on.
(Amy:)I think I might have
a little surprise
(Amy:)that might help get things
back on track.
(Sheldon:)Intriguing.
Is “back on track” a hint
(Sheldon:)that it has something
to do with trains?
(Bernadette:)No.
(Sheldon:)Because if it did have to do
with trains, and you were
(Sheldon:)gonna give...
It's not about trains!
Oh. Not even a cozy sleeper
car on the Orient Express?
(Amy:)Stop talking
about trains!
(Sheldon:)Who's killing the mood now?
(Leonard:)Found the backup inhaler.
Want to have sex?
(Penny:)Well, I didn't
until I heard that.
(Leonard:)Hang on. I'm counting.